Jeffrey Lu

Full-Stack Developer

Brooklyn, NY
lu.jeffrey91@gmail.com
(718) 415-8521
LinkedIn
Github | Portfolio

Full-Stack Developer with a background in shipping and logistics. I bring my experience of notable attention to detail, partaking in handling moving parts through production. I relish in the satisfaction of a completed project and patience that comes with it. Combining these experiences, I hope to create more ease of access applications for people across the globe.

SKILLS

- Front-End: React.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python
- Back-End: Heroku, MongoDB
- Libraries: PostgresSQL, Django, Express.js, Node.js
- Version control utilizing GIT
- Soft Skills: Customer Service, Customer relations support, Negotiations, Multilingual

PROJECTS

Taco Jump: https://jiffylube.github.io/Taco-Jump/

- Front end game based off of google chrome's dinosaur game
- Built using Javascript, CSS, HTML

Monster Hunter World Project: https://friendly-pie-4f7f43.netlify.app/

- Front end API app that allows users to fetch data from a database
- Designed using React.js

mySelfie: https://thunderous-cendol-805368.netlify.app/

- Full-Stack application that allows users to take selfies
- Front-end built using React.js, react routers
- Back-end built using Node, Express, and mongoose API

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, New York, NY

Software Engineering Fellow, March 2022 - May 2022

- Designed user facing projects utilizing Javascript and React.js
- Set up back-end website applications, and setup databases using MongoDB, SQL, with other frameworks.
- Collaborated with small teams for building acceptable products within allotted deadlines.
- Managed version control technology for self and group projects with Git and GitHub.

Apex Logistics International, Springfield, NY

Ocean Imports Team Lead, July 2018 - July 2021

Ocean Imports Coordinator, August 2016 - June 2018

- Provided cross country shipping solutions to ensure customer deadlines are met.
- Managed large scale projects for distribution center requirements, and ensured consistent routing options are readily available.
- Handled numerous Dangerous Goods shipments, DG certified.

EDUCATION

General Assembly, *Software Engineering Immersive* | New York, NY | March 2022 - May 2022 **New York City College of Technology,** *Electrical Engineering* | New York, NY | August 2009 - June 2011 **Brooklyn Technical High School,** *Majored in Architecture* | New York, NY | August 2005 - June 2009